<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/css' href='css/xml.css' ?>
<News>
	<Item>
		<Title>Gokulashtami </Title>
		<Date>August 12th, 2012</Date>
		<Details>Lokmanya Mandal had organised Gokulashtami on Sunday 12th August for everybody's convinience and maximum participation.</Details>	
		<link>intermediate.jsp?index=1</link>
		<content>Lokmanya Mandal had organised Gokulashtami on Sunday 12th August 2012. 
		The reponse for average as always, but everybody turned out to feast on "Dahikala".</content>
		<index>1</index>
	</Item>		
	<Item>
		<Title>Bhagini Mandal's 60th Anniversary </Title>
		<Date>December 1st, 2012</Date>		
		<Details>To celebrate 60th Annniversary of Lokmanya Bhagini Mandal, the mandal on behalf of all members proposes to conduct ....</Details>		
		<link>intermediate.jsp?index=2</link>
		<content>To celebrate 60th Annniversary of Lokmanya Bhagini Mandal, the mandal on behalf of all members proposes to conduct "Mahervashini - Sasurvashini" melava on 1st December 2012.
					This is a paid event (approximate contribution is Rupees. 400 per person). For more details, contact:-
						Mrs. Sushama Joshi - 9769362601
						Mrs. Sharwani Kane - 9820218208
						Mrs. Shadhana Bhagwat - 9833448825					
					All Mahervashini's and Sasurvashini's are cordially invited.... Lets have a day of fun, remembrances and lets relive old memories....
					</content>
		<index>2</index>
	</Item>		
	<Item>
		<Title>I building Lift</Title>
		<Date>October 24th, 2012</Date>
		<Details>Hurray...!!! Much awaited I building lift was inaugurated on Wednesday, 24th Oct 2012</Details>	
		<link>intermediate.jsp?index=3</link>
		<content>Much awaited I building lift which is already up and running, was officially inaugurated on Wednesday, 24th October 2012.
				Inauguration was done by our society's President Mr. Mr. Purshottam Namjoshi.
				This is a Hydraulic lift with a capacity of 3-4 people, its one of the most unique project undertaken by our society.
				The Society will always remain thankful to Mr. Prakash Kanitkar, Dr. Kamlakar Dandekar and everybody else for their efforts to achieve something
				which was once considered as a risk.</content>
		<index>3</index>
	</Item>		
	<Item>
		<Title>Dasera Pooja</Title>	
		<Date>October 24th, 2012</Date>		
		<Details>Lokmanya Mandal had organised Dasera Pooja on 24th October 2012</Details>
		<link>intermediate.jsp?index=4</link>
		<content>Lokmanya Mandal had organised Dasera Pooja on 24th October 2012. This year's Dasera pooja was performed by Mr. Ashwin and Mrs. Shradha Joglekar</content>
		<index>4</index>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Title>Ganeshotsav</Title>	
		<Date>September 19th, 2012</Date>		
		<Details>Ganpati Bappa Moraya.. All are requested to mail all the photos related to Ganeshotsav</Details>
		<link>intermediate.jsp?index=5</link>
		<content>All members are requested to mail all photos of this years Ganeshotsav on 'admin@lokmanyanagar.com'. These photos will be published on our society website.</content>
		<index>5</index>
	</Item>
</News> 